Logan Parker

Loganparker.ca Vancouver, British Columbia

Logan@loganparker.ca

Profile

Enthusiastic and adaptable BCom graduate from the University of British Columbia with a specialization in Finance and Real Estate. Driven by a desire for overcoming obstacles and achieving goals in both personal and professional settings. Thrives in collaborative and independent environments.

Education

Bachelor of Commerce, Finance and Real Estate (Honours) University of British Columbia, Vancouver, BC

Completed April 2016

• Dean's Honour Roll 2015, 2016.

Work Experience

Associate, SchoolSoft Inc., Calgary, AB (Contract) September 2012—August 2013, August 2016—Present

- Testing the new online student-permission-form software on an ongoing basis, reporting major issues and changes directly to the founders.
- Creating and distributing invoices on an ongoing basis to clients in North America and Europe.
- Configured 250 customers' accounts for the parent-teacher-interview scheduling software.

Investment Analyst, Premise Properties, Vancouver, BC

May 2015—August 2015

- Managed the renovation of 30 balconies and the roof of a 40-unit residential property over a fourmonth period. Responsibilities included scheduling and coordinating vendors and payment.
- Led the due diligence process on the sale of a major commercial property in Vancouver.
- Analyzed all current real estate investments within the company in order to assess current asset value and performance versus expected value and performance.

Operations Manager, Cowichan Lake Marina, Lake Cowichan, BC (Seasonal) May 2010—August 2014

- Ordered, managed, and sold \$25,000 worth of merchandise per season for the marina's retail store.
- Met sales and cost-cutting goals through constant communication with suppliers, staff, and owners.

Activities and Community Involvement

Vice President & External Public Relations, UBC Ski and Snowboard Club April 2013—March 2015

- Raised \$2,500 for Vancouver Adaptive Snow Sports (VASS) by organizing and executing a skiing and snowboarding contest at UBC with over 400 spectators and 40 contestants.
- Built and maintained a relationship with 28 sponsors throughout the calendar year for the UBC Ski and Snowboard Club—one of UBC's largest student-run clubs.

Skills and Interests

Skills: Presenting and public speaking, Microsoft Office, basic HTML and CSS, basic Python, basic SQL.

Interests: Cycling: After graduating from UBC I cycled 3,100 kilometers from Vancouver, BC

to the border of Mexico near San Diego.

Surfing: I spent kindergarten to grade five growing up near Santa Cruz, California,

where I learned to surf and continue to do so on Vancouver Island.

Traveling: I spent the summer following graduation traveling USA and Europe.